citylocal.co.uk 2010-03-05

# City Local UK - Privacy Policy

This privacy policy explains what information has been collected about you, how personal information is being used, to whom personal information is being disclosed and how this personal information is stored and protected. This privacy policy has been developed in accordance with our legal obligations and may be updated from time to time. This policy applies whether or not you choose to advertise on anycitylocal.co.uk site.  
By accessing and utilising the citylocal.co.uk website and any subsidiary sites maintained by authorised franchisees trading under the style “citylocal.co.uk” you consent to the use of any data collected as set out in this policy. You should review this privacy policy regularly, to note any changes relating to how we collect and use information.    

**Personal Information**

In order to process and complete your request for an advertisement listing certain information, such as your name, address, telephone number; and email address, will be required. We will use this information to contact you in case of a query relating to your advertisement and to process you request to post an advertisement on citylocal.co.uk. We use your personal information to help us understand more about how our web site is used, to improve our site, and to send you information about us and our products which we think may be of interest to you, both electronically or otherwise. Unless you have informed us that you do not wish to receive further information about our products, we may send you direct mail. If you do not wish to have your information used for these purposes, you may elect to opt-out from future communications by notifying CityLocal Limited in writing to the registered address: 1 Ralston Mount, Broughty Ferry, Dundee, DD5 1NN or by e-mailing nazir@citylocal.co.uk  
citylocal.co.uk will never offer a third party access to this information for any purpose, and citylocal.co.uk will only store information necessary to operate effectively in our main database. If however we believe that your use of the site is unlawful or damaging to others, we reserve the right to disclose the information we have obtained through the site about you to the extent that it is reasonably necessary in our opinion to prevent, remedy or take action in relation to such conduct.

**Public Information**

Listings information submitted for display on the citylocal.co.uk website is information for the public domain and therefore cannot be classed as private. If we request any information which could be classed as private, citylocal.co.uk will make you aware of this at the time of submission.   

**Third Party Links**

Any sites you link to through citylocal.co.uk are not within our control and are not covered by this privacy statement. We urge you to review each site's privacy policy before entering into transactions with them.  

**Browsing the Site**

As you browse the website, we collect information about your use of the site for usability studies and marketing. Essentially this will be what pages you have visited and how long you stay online. We will not be able to identify who you are, but we will be able to identify where you are located. Whether you advertise with Citylocal or not, our web server collects certain information such as your IP address, browser type or referring URL. We may provide anonymous statistics about user's browsing activity to reputable third party vendors, but these will not include details that would allow the recipient to identify you.  

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small quantity of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a website's computer and stored on your computer's hard drive. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.   
cityloal.co.uk uses cookies to identify whether you have visited the site previously and to target content tailored to your interests. If you do not want us to use cookies in your browser, you can set your browser to reject cookies or to tell you when a website tries to put a cookie on your computer. Cookie information will not be disclosed or sold to third parties without your consent.   

**Company and Data Protection Information**   

The data controller of data on the citylocal.co.uk is CityLocal Limited, a company in the registered in Scotland under company number SC312837, whose registered office is at 1 Ralston Mount, Broughty Ferry, Dundee, DD5 1NN. Any queries or notices under the Data Protection Act 1998 should be sent to the above address. 

|
